(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
(In the south of France,)
(the azure Mediterranean coastline)
(stretches for hundreds of kilometers.)
(Sunlight spills over the valleys,)
(vineyards and ancient towns,)
(creating its exclusive romantic vibe.)
(From the lavender fields of Provence)
(to the harbor scenery
along the French Riviera,)
(South France paints people's yearning)
(for a wonderful life)
(with freedom,)
(enthusiasm and exquisite elegance.)
(Today,)
(the Earth Group heads down
to Southern France,)
(stepping into)
(this sun-kissed land)
(to embark on a journey)
(filled with sunshine and ocean views.)
=Episode 8 (Part 1)=
(Sunshine and Sea in the South of France)
(The Earth Group's guesthouse)
Really beautiful.
This place is so beautiful.
Why is the sea so blue?
Good morning.
Morning, sir.
Do you remember the lines
from Romeo and Juliet?
Go ahead.
(Guo Jingfei)
You. You say it.
I'm Juliet.
(Juliet is in position)
Ju...
[*Sounds like "wish" in Chinese]
♪Wishing you a happy birthday♪
Beautiful?
Beautiful.
So beautiful.
It feels like it's just your house.
"Beautiful?"
(Don't rush)
I'm asking,
"Am I beautiful?"
But you have to admit that
this place is really nice.
Morning.
This looks like Wi-Fi signal.
Bro.
Morning.
Did we ruin your mood?
I know you wanted
to enjoy the scenery for a while alone.
(Who can control him?)
He's so annoying.
Sit down for a while.
Have a seat.
Alright, guys.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Go jump in the sea.
Jump into the sea.
Oh, my.
They've already set off, right?
Yes.
Hello.
(Deng Kai)
Welcome, Deng Kai,
- to Wow The World S2.
- Wait.
Which camera should I look at?
This one?
Or that one?
Up to you.
Look at this one.
This one.
How about it?
Hello.
(Deng Kai: Pursuit of Jade,
The Wanted Detective, Love the Divine Tree)
(How did you feel)
(when you got the show invite?)
Really refreshing.
It felt really refreshing.
Because I'm...
Actually, overall,
I wouldn't call this my very first
variety show appearance,
but
it's the first one I've taken part in
that has a longer filming schedule
than previous ones.
Before, I usually finished filming
in just one or two days.
I'm a bit nervous.
(Seek verification)
You can tell, right?
I can't tell.
(What's your impression)
(of visiting France for the first time?)
Actually, I studied French for a month,
but I only remember a few simple words.
(Hello)
Bonjour.
(How are you)
Ça va.
(Thank you)
Merci.
(Hi)
Salut.
That's it.
Yesterday, Chen Xingxu
even sent me a message.
He said,
"If you need anything,
just let me know."
"I'll definitely take good care of you."
And I said, "I'll cling tight to you
and rely entirely on you."
He said, "No problem."
I checked out earlier episodes
and noticed something weird.
He never wins any games.
Such a game noob.
(What expectations do you have
for this trip?)
Enjoy sights I've never seen before.
This is truly my first time
visiting here.
I'd only seen these sights
online before,
and now I'm seeing them in real life.
I plan to take lots of photos.
If you don't get good shots
when you travel somewhere,
can you prove you've actually been here?
(Yang Chaoyue: Being Towards Death)
I was here filming not long ago,
(Born to Run, Love You Seven Times)
but only stayed in Nice back then.
I thought
the scenery here was very beautiful,
and it has a totally different vibe
from Paris.
So I hope to be here
with friends
to take in
the views
and try the fun stuff.
See.
All iPhones.
(Photographer's
carry-on essentials revealed)
Every generation of iPhone
works perfectly
as my photography partner.
It's iPhone's
"grandpa".
It's iPhone's "daddy".
(Family sticks together as a whole)
I have all generations.
Each one features a unique filter
representing its era.
It's all about the vibe.
Don't you get it?
You don't get it.
(Are you familiar with Earth Group members?)
Yuwen
is my good friend.
(Dear friend)
We've met a few times on variety shows,
but we hang out
more often in private.
I used to film dramas with Yuning,
and we...
We've taken part in
some variety shows together.
And then,
same as Fei.
We used to record variety shows
together quite often.
And
I only met Naiwen once
during a variety show recording,
so we're not that close.
But he strikes me
as a really competitive
(Why?)
older gentleman.
Well...
(Turns out to be nothing)
He takes games really seriously.
First, welcome everyone to South France.
Besides,
two new friends
will be joining us today.
Our first guest
is a vibrant young girl
with an incredibly fun personality.
Yang Chaoyue.
Hello.
Come on over.
Hello, everyone.
The Mischievous Silver Shaded Cat.
(Me?)
A man you love and hate all at once.
Deng Kai.
(Still from the drama Pursuit of Jade)
Love and hate.
Here we go, guys.
What?
"Here we go, guys."
Why does this feel so familiar?
Are we still in France?
What's wrong?
(Don't say that)
"Here we go, guys."
Hello, guys.
Hello.
Come sit in the middle.
To the middle.
Come on.
"Here we go, guys."
Bro.
Come on.
Hello.
(Nice to meet you)
They've never met before.
Alright.
Come on, sit down, everyone.
Have a seat.
H-Have a seat?
Just sit down directly?
You two introduce yourselves to everyone
and mention whose friend you are.
Hello, everyone. I'm Yang Chaoyue.
And
I'm Yuwen's friend,
Yuning's friend,
Fei's friend,
and...
(Manual hint)
That's all.
That's... Well, that's all.
Lin Yi.
(Lin Yi)
We haven't
met privately.
We're just online friends.
There is some connection between us.
Yeah, a little bit.
I am
(Lin Yi and Huang Minghao)
the Troublemaker Number 1.
(Footage sourced online)
Right, I am Number 2.
(Yang Chaoyue and Huang Minghao)
Hello.
(Li Naiwen)
Let me ask you a question on behalf of Honglei.
What's your zodiac sign?
I'm a Leo.
Leo.
Honglei.
When is your birthday?
July 31st.
Leo head.
You don't mean to cook her up, do you?
[*Refer to a dish called braised lion's head]
My birthday is August 16th.
Leo body.
Why does this feel exactly like
a blind date show?
What's wrong? Are you jealous?
I didn't cue you at all.
No.
We are father and daughter.
That was in the past.
This is a new show.
Stop dragging me into your business.
Alright.
Okay, let me do it.
Okay.
Hello, everyone. I'm Deng Kai.
And I...
I am from the Northeast.
Hometown buddy.
Yeah, hometown buddy.
I have plenty of hometown buddies here.
And I'm Xingxu's friend.
We once filmed a series together.
Nice to meet you all.
Which city in the Northeast
are you from?
I'm from Dalian.
Dalian.
It's also a coastal city.
Okay.
Come on.
Everyone,
the most iconic attraction
in South France
is the French Riviera.
Our whole itinerary today
will revolve around
this stunning coastline.
(Chen Xingxu)
Since we've got new guests joining us,
our bond needs to grow
little by little.
Makes sense.
(From pool to the sea)
So we begin with freshwater, then head to the sea.
(Well said)
The sunshine and sea
along the French Riviera
come with a natural cinematic filter.
(Wang Yuwen)
This is also the birthplace
of the world-famous
Cannes Film Festival.
Next, we will carry out a mission.
I believe everyone here
has filmed rain scenes before.
In TV dramas and movies,
shifts in weather settings
are often used to reflect the lead
characters' inner emotional swings.
The next mission
is all about rain scenes,
which is called
Man in Rain on the Floating Platform.
In each round, the program team
will play
classic clips featuring
iconic rain scenes.
After watching it by the swimming pool,
(Performance Platform)
the first two onto the floating platform
will recreate the scenes.
(Liu Yuning)
They can earn points
only if their emotions in reenactment
match the intensity
of the original clip.
Honglei
got more than 30 injuries
all over his body.
You got over 30 injuries.
(Don't believe rumors or spread them)
So Honglei
is the Rain God for this mission.
I am the Rain God.
Yes.
You are in charge of making it rain.
Honglei.
(You know what I mean)
How heavy the rain is...
(Listen to Fei)
Will he listen to you?
Last time, the Best Actress
(Best Actress?)
put on an excellent performance.
Best Actress, Nai.
Me!
Yes, Mud Pit Best Actress.
The ever-present leading lady.
(The Mud Pit Best Actress
must be Naiwen)
Mud Pit Best Actress.
Scene-stealer.
So, shouldn't I
(I'm not backing down this time)
give more chances to younger members?
(Nai's intentions are plain to all)
It'd be great if you knew how to behave properly.
(Can't wait)
Let's go.
Jump in the pool.
My heart is thumping wildly.
(Can't figure out
what you're so excited for)
(Joining in)
(Landlubber Yuning)
It's so deep.
(It only comes up to your knee)
(Mischievous ideas brewing)
You dare mess with me? Are you crazy?
Why wouldn't I dare tease
you out here in the water?
(Opportunity knocks)
You're so...
(But once)
She chickens out easily but can't resist joining in fun.
I really don't want to target her.
(The consequence of provoking me)
Forget it.
(Just a small provocation)
It's tough to climb up onto it.
It is movable.
Only Nai can be the first one
to set foot on it.
(Best Actress's self-awareness)
Yes, I just try it first.
Too obvious your motive.
The rainfall is way too heavy.
(The Rain God is all set)
Can you guys turn around and look at me?
(Angry Rain God means big trouble)
Do I not exist at all?
I looked.
I saw you.
You guys don't take me seriously.
I feel totally invisible.
You are so cool just now.
Hail the Rain God.
(Cheered up instantly)
Come on.
(The Best Actress can't wait any longer)
(Round 1)
(Clips from Princess Hours)
Wow, it's really delicious!
You're such a genius.
It's really delicious.
No way.
No way. What a coincidence.
It's raining right now.
Shall we head inside
to shelter from the rain?
Why bother?
It'd be such a waste
not to finish this delicious food.
(Language system is being upgraded)
Who says we can't feast in the rain?
Why are there so many words?
We still have to dance.
Ballroom dancing in the rain.
(Everyone, keep your cheek muscles
relaxed and flat)
So romantic.
How about we get romantic as well?
(Always ready)
Come on, get ready.
(The Best Actress goes first)
Go.
(Staring intently)
Look at Nai's eyes.
Anyone who truly wants to win
won't crack a smile.
(Determined to win)
Five.
It'd be such a waste
not to finish this delicious food.
Four.
Three.
Two.
(Rain God is ready)
One.
(Stage, Nai is coming)
(Yuning is here)
(Deng Kai is here too)
(No one else stands a chance)
(Suffered a Waterloo)
How could you do this?
(Waiting for the right moment to strike)
(Trying to lift)
Come on, I'll hold it for you.
(Chen Xingxu and Lin Yi
step onto the floating platform)
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Act it out like this?
Alright, come on.
Lin Yi and Xingxu.
Are you playing the guy or the girl?
I play the guy.
You play the guy?
Let's stay away from them.
Otherwise, we'll be in the rain.
(Safe distance)
(Ready to rain at any moment)
Come on, girlfriend.
I haven't learned the girl's part.
I didn't memorize the girl's lines.
Didn't memorize a single line?
I didn't memorize a single line.
(They're arguing)
Think it over.
Get down, come on.
Get down.
Wait.
I'll do it.
How did Nai get up there?
(The Best Actress never gives up)
Come on.
Are you playing the guy or the girl?
I play the guy.
Okay.
(Not a freeze frame)
Wait a minute.
Are you going to act or not?
I'll do it.
He speaks first.
The girl delivers the line first.
I'm playing the male role.
I...
I speak first?
Turn it.
Right.
Don't grab it.
Turn it.
Come on, scene-stealer.
This...
Come on, get ready.
(Forced to start: "Princess Hours")
It's really delicious.
Jin, you're truly a genius.
No way.
(It's raining)
It’s raining! Naiwen, hurry.
Coming!
(Rain God is coming)
Step back.
No.
(Scattering like birds)
It's raining!
No way!
Such a coincidence.
Why must it rain now?
No way!
(A sudden downpour)
I'll protect you.
("Princess Hours")
No way!
Why must it rain now?
Should we go inside and wait it out?
Why should we?
Maybe we should do that.
Let them drift away,
all the way back to Beijing.
Why should we go inside?
Can’t we just have a feast right here?
Exactly.
Who says we can’t enjoy our meal
in heavy rain?
Come dance.
Dance.
(Looking for something to hold onto)
(Auto-following)
(Slick hair)
(Keep raining)
I can't hold on anymore.
(Stop)
This job is pretty nice.
(Fragile moments make you fragile)
Did we score points?
(Li Naiwen: 1 point, Lin Yi: 1 point)
Yes. One point each.
(Already exhausted)
(Round 2)
(Clips from "Scarlet Heart")
It starts raining at the beginning.
(The Rain God is satisfied)
In this storm,
there’s someone beside me
to endure it,
to suffer, to hold on.
To hold on.
Go back.
I know your heart.
Only the actress has lines.
The actor doesn’t have any.
I want to play the man.
That works for me.
(Ready to fight)
(Come on)
Okay, come on.
Three, two, one.
(Guo Jingfei takes the spot first)
I'll play the man.
(Key target)
(Off you go)
(You too)
Come down.
(Seizing the stage)
Drag him down.
Fei, how about we act together?
(Surprisingly polite)
Who's memorized the lines?
Have you?
Come on. Get up.
In this storm, there’s someone
beside me to endure it.
No.
It has to be me.
Let me.
(Off you go)
Come on.
Let Deng Kai have a go.
(Your Kai is here)
Here I come.
Get him down.
Stage ruler.
Stage boss.
In this...
(Unexpected disaster)
(Currently no one
on the floating platform)
(Never giving up)
Come on.
(Afraid of water. Leave first)
(Don't go)
I don’t want to!
Come on.
I...
(Emergency management)
My pants fell down.
(Too heavy rain. I'll go first)
No.
Wait!
Let's go.
(Where are you going?)
A little rain. Please.
It can’t keep pouring.
♪The little rain comes at the right time♪
(Let you off the hook)
Yes.
(Nai comes again)
Come.
(Pulling)
(Get down!)
(Snickering)
Alright.
(Chen Xingxu and Wang Yuwen
step onto the floating platform)
Okay.
I'm not fighting. Just watch.
(Sincere)
I'm telling you,
this is actually
a great comedy practice.
You guys have to take it seriously.
Come on.
Let's start.
Don't laugh.
Show some professionalism.
Okay.
Come on.
(Scarlet Heart)
Be serious.
You must be serious.
(Serious)
Yes, good, really great.
Yes, splash his face.
(Seizing every opportunity)
I'll do it.
Come on, Jingfei.
Hurry.
(Secured the role
of the silent male lead)
So majestic.
They look like two flowerpots.
He’s watering the flowers.
(Scarlet Heart)
In this storm,
there’s someone beside me
to endure it,
to suffer,
to hold on.
(Automatic avoiding)
Go back.
I know your heart.
Great.
Awesome.
(Glamorous exit)
Good.
(Chinese People Can Fly)
You even can do this?
Mermaid release.
I feel like a dolphin.
Sorry,
Impressive.
Really cool, Jingfei.
(Li Naiwen: 1, Lin Y: 1, Wang Yuwen: 1, Guo Jingfei: 1)
(Handsome, no need to say)
(Round 3)
(Clips from "It Started with a Kiss")
How could it have nothing to do with me?
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else!
You're always so confident.
What is this?
The person I like is you.
the person I like is you.
But what can I do?
but what can I do?
You don't like me at all.
Don't.
Don't fall for someone else.
This needs a height difference.
Let's go home.
I think this scene
would be better underwater.
(Shy)
Ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
I won't fight for this.
(I' m just a kid)
Everyone's shy.
Look.
No one is fighting
for it.
Go.
Okay.
Come on.
Aren't you going to fight?
(Fighting for a better view)
Wait, come back.
(The stage is yours)
Nobody wants.
Wait.
(Is this right?)
I can be the kissing double.
Kissing double.
Chaoyue, I'll be yours.
Okay.
Come.
(Holding on)
Can I hold up your face for a moment?
(can’t watch people I know do this)
("It Started with a Kiss")
How could it have nothing to do with me?
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else!
("It Started with a Kiss" take second)
You're always so confident.
I'm going to cry.
What are you going to do?
My mouth.
My mouth is full of water.
Ready, start over.
("It Started with a Kiss" take third)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else!
You're always so confident.
(What was the line?)
What is this?
Even I have memorized it.
You really want to act.
(Always ready)
I do like you,
but you don't like me at all.
Don't.
Don't fall for someone else.
Come on. Get up.
Come!
(Absorbed. Immersed)
Here we come.
You two squat down first. Yes.
Xingxu squat down first.
Then stand up later.
(Make room)
Right.
And then?
Kiss.
(Can't bear to watch)
Then squat down.
Then you.
Come.
Chaoyue, come.
(The leads are back)
Pick it up.
Let's go home.
Great.
Awesome.
Can we get half a point for this?
(Need double's fee)
Yes, give us half a point.
You have to do the whole scene to count.
(Not hesitating for even one second)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
Come.
The person you like is me.
Get down.
You get down.
(The stage is ours)
You're no longer useful.
Come.
Say it.
(Title: It Started with Another Kiss
Actors: Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
Why is Fei
keeping one eye closed?
(One-eyed acting)
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else!
Fei is spitting water out.
Don't.
You're always so confident.
What is this?
(Strong counterattack)
How do you know the person I like
isn't you?
You don't like me at all.
Don't!
Don't fall for someone else!
Kiss!
Kiss.
(Stunned)
(Waiting for praise)
Age brings wisdom.
I need to learn from you.
I did make an artistic choice.
It's a deep kiss.
So we made it underwater.
Sealing it with a kiss.
Fei only has one eye open.
What happened to your left eye?
Can't bear to look with both eyes?
Must keep one eye shut.
(I don’t dare open it.
Hopefully this is just my imagination)
how's this score?
Great.
Good, right?
(Li Naiwen: 2, Guo Jingfei: 2, Chen Xingxu: 1)
Good.
(Wang Yuwen: 1, Lin Yi: 1, Yang Chaoyue: 1)
Not easy.
(Round 4)
(Clips from
"The Legend of the White Snake")
Boatman! Boatman!
Quick, give me the umbrella
from the cabin.
Sister.
Two people?
This one.
- It's three people.
- Take it.
Three people.
The two of us go then.
(Reserved)
The two sisters.
- The weather is unpredictable.
- A and B roles.
- Take it quickly.
- There's also a C role.
Yes, there's a C role.
So many roles?
-Then hurry back.
Sir!
-Sir, how can I return it to you?
- How can I return it to you?
I’ll come back for it later.
- I’ll come back for it later.
- Okay.
(Naiwen getting ready)
- Okay. -Deal.
Remember, Shuangrong Alley, Bai Residence.
Okay.
Three people.
Let's go first.
Come.
(Come on, Xiaoqing)
Get the two female roles first.
Okay.
Come on, get ready.
Three.
(Yuning, give it a try)
(Scared)
I'm afraid to get down.
Two.
One.
Go.
(Your elder sister here)
(Your little sister is here)
(Your Nainai is here too)
He comes again. It's him again.
It's a group scene.
(This isn't too much, is it?)
You're everywhere.
You get him off.
Group scene.
(I just love acting)
(Demon's Hand)
(Don't come here!)
(Demon's Foot)
(Get down!)
(Speak up for me)
(Then I'll do it)
We need a handsome guy.
(You know me)
(Fate, you're so fake)
(Fate, you're such a pain)
Why?
Go, Yuning, go!
Okay, I'll try.
Wait.
Okay.
I'm the little sister.
(Liu Yuning as Xu Xian)
Okay.
(Wang Yuwen as Bai Suzhen, Yang Chaoyue as Xiaoqing)
Wait a moment.
Give me the umbrella.
Umbrella!
I'll play the boatman.
(A good actor doesn't pick roles)
Sure.
You're so into it.
(Acting addiction)
Boatman.
Quick, give me the umbrella
from the cabin.
Give me the umbrella!
Here you go.
(Acting again)
"The Legend of the White Snake"
Miss.
(Unbearable)
Take this umbrella.
Okay?
(Are you sure
this umbrella actually works?)
(What a refreshing shower)
What about you?
Hahaha.
It's fine for me.
The weather is unpredictable.
(Real artificial rain)
Just take it.
(Someone please control them)
How can I accept this?
Boatman.
(Intensifying the attack)
You are so naughty, boatman.
(Help me)
Wait.
Where are we?
(Can't wait a second)
That's enough.
Hurry, say your lines.
(You're C, hurry)
(C Role)
(C is here)
Who is C?
Xiaoqing.
(Or maybe not there)
Hurry.
Say your lines, Xiaoqing.
Sir, this umbrella of yours...
Sir.
Speak quickly.
Sir, the umbrella...
The umbrella...
(Attack again)
How can I return it to you?
Say your lines.
Overcome the distractions.
Actors must concentrate.
It's fine.
I’ll come back for it later.
(Not convinced)
Step back.
(Can't take it anymore)
Back off!
Back off! Back off!
Hurry up. Finish it.
Hurry. I'm scared.
Hurry.
Okay.
Okay, then you must remember
Shuangrong Alley, Bai Residence.
Bai Residence.
Okay.
(Finally it's over)
(This is not a place to linger)
(Where are you running to?)
Guo Jingfei!
I'm getting down.
(Danger)
Splash.
Splash me?
Splashing?
(I’d do it again next time)
(Li Naiwen: 2, Guo Jingfei: 2, Wang Yuwen: 2
Yang Chaoyue: 2, Liu Yuning: 1, Chen Xingxu: 1, Lin Yi: 1)
(Round 5)
(Clips from "Secret")
This is Jay Chou's...
"Secret".
Do you want me to give you a ride
on my way?
- How do you know it's on the way?
Why did it start raining suddenly?
You don't have an umbrella?
How to act this?
- He's going to run.
- Why aren't you saying anything?
Whatever I ask you,
you always say it’s a secret.
So, do you like
sunny days or rainy days?
Both.
Fine.
(First to take the stage)
Come on. Get ready.
Let it rain.
Camera, ready.
(Camera is ready)
Action.
(Secret)
Do you want me to give you a ride
on my way?
How do you know it's on the way?
Why did it start raining suddenly?
You didn't bring an umbrella?
Why'd you go quiet all of a sudden?
(I think it's okay)
You're in character, good actor.
(Mime performance)
Which musician do you like?
I like them all.
How was it?
Great!
(Naiwen 2, Guo Jingfei 2, Chen Xingxu 2
Wang Yuwen 2, Lin Yi 2, Yang Chaoyue 2)
(Liu Yuning 1, Deng Kai 0)
(Currently the only zero-point player)
(Round 6)
(Clips from Forbidden City Summit)
Ying,
you shouldn't have come at all.
Learn this part.
This part.
Dance?
Dance battle.
What's this?
(Already practicing)
What?
Stop!
Stop it!
Stop fighting!
Stop!
(Must secure it)
I'll dance too.
I'll dance with you.
Okay, come on.
I have to shout like,
"Shut up!
Stop fighting!"
(Carefully)
OK.
Okay.
(The audience is ready)
Coming.
- I'll squat down first.
- Three, two, one.
(Forbidden City Summit)
Ying,
you shouldn't have come!
Let's switch places. Come on.
You come over to my side.
Come on.
(Smoothly switching positions)
Okay, come on.
Come on. Dance.
Come on.
Floor moves.
Stop!
Stop fighting!
(If you're itchy, go take a shower)
I beg you! Please stop!
I'll punch you.
You block me.
Okay.
(Manual slow motion)
I'll dodge.
Then...
You punch me.
Okay.
Hook.
Duck.
Okay.
No!
Stop fighting!
(Stop this farce)
Okay, okay.
Not dancing fiercely enough.
Not fierce enough?
Still not fierce enough?
That's enough.
(Losing all strength)
I score a point.
Right.
(Deng Kai 1)
Okay.
Everyone, we're heading out to the sea.
Let's go.
(Caring Yuning appears)
What's wrong with you?
My scalp feels a bit uncomfortable.
Try this.
Head & Shoulders Scalp Care Oil Control.
It has special ingredients.
(Salicylic acid, Approval)
Molecules penetrate deep into the scalp,
inhibiting oil production
and ensuring hair is fluffy, fresh,
and weightless.
(Can't wait)
Then I must try it.
(Appreciating)
How is it, Lin Yi?
Is it good?
Head & Shoulders Scalp Care Oil Control
is really good.
(Satisfied)
After washing, it's super refreshing.
My hair just fluffs up.
That's for sure.
Oil control and fluffiness.
Awesome.
Let's go.
Come on.
Isn't this headband tight?
No.
It was so tight I couldn't stand it.
Like in Chinese opera.
Upturned eyes.
What's your head circumference?
What's his?
Yeah.
Fei, what's your head circumference?
I'm 58 centimeters.
I'm 59 centimeters.
(Bigger than me?)
But I have to wear a 59 centimeter hat.
A 58 centimeters hat
is a bit uncomfortable for me.
Then it's 59 centimeters.
What do you mean I'm 58 centimeters,
but it's uncomfortable to wear?
I also feel uncomfortable
wearing a 58 centimeter hat.
Lei.
Yue.
Ms. Wang.
What Wang?
Why Yue and Ms. Wang?
How did I end up among kids?
(The post-90s army is all here)
Does Chaoyue sing well?
Yes, she sings very well.
Really, Wen?
(Arrived at Vieux Port)
Here we are.
So quiet.
When the seagulls cry...
Beautiful.
Really beautiful.
The water is really clear.
Such a quiet bay
is rare.
Really beautiful.
Actually, you see, after filming
and wrapping up,
it's quite relaxing
to come here.
Yes, quite comfortable.
Right? It's quite stress-relieving.
The first time in my life
I started to like the sea
was in Marseille.
Because the water was too calm.
I wonder how our little sheep is now
in New Zealand.
Wow.
(Missing everyone)
It should be quite big now, right?
I see our boat.
♪Bling bling, it's me♪
♪Bling bling, what are you doing♪
Okay, you go have fun.
I'll have sunflower seeds here.
This water is perfect for swimming.
Right.
Later, I'll take you
somewhere with clearer water.
(Let's go right away)
Let's go.
At this moment, we are
at the Mediterranean waters
off Saint-Cyr-sur-Mer.
The sea is not only
about the gentle and romantic scenery
by the shore.
Now, we're going
to ride the wind and waves,
push beyond our limits,
and embrace the challenge of the sea.
Later, you'll
have the option
to try parasailing.
(Parasailing)
- This one.
- Is it parasailing?
(Want to try)
This one isn't scary.
I want to try this one.
(Want to try +1)
Who wants to play with me?
Parasailing
can take you up to 100 meters
above the sea.
(Excited)
100 meters?
Yes.
(A bit scary)
That isn't necessary, right?
There's also wakeboarding.
(Wakeboarding)
This is so hard.
We actually need to learn this.
I want to try.
I can't do it.
This is okay.
This is so cool.
There's also jet skiing.
(Jet ski)
I'll try jet skiing.
There's also tube rafting.
(Tube rafting)
But you just need to sit on it.
This is fun.
Honglei, let's do it.
Come on.
Happy again, Honglei.
I'll go play that one.
I've checked these four.
They all seem fine.
Who wants to try parasailing with me?
Me.
Okay.
- Me.
- Okay.
- You and me.
- We two are Leos.
You're not going?
Parasailing.
I won't ride. You guys play.
Even I dare to do the parasailing.
Really?
(Scared)
Yeah.
Even I dare to do it.
You can get ready for wakeboarding.
Come on.
I'm coming.
Hello.
You can sit here.
Okay.
And you can stand upon here.
Alright.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye-bye.
Are you coming back, Xingxu?
Have an orange.
(Quite enthusiastic)
(A lovely bouquet of words)
(Training with a professional coach)
(Filmed under training
and full supervision)
Stand up.
(Chen Xingxu tries wakeboarding)
Let's go.
Good.
(Succeed on the first try)
He's already standing up.
So impressive.
So cool.
He's so good. He stood up right away.
Where?
I like it.
Let's go.
You guys play.
Yuning, just stay in the middle.
We'll protect you.
Take a look first.
Go for it, Yuning?
We're doing the relaxing drift.
Right.
At the pace you want.
Is that okay?
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
(Decided to give it a try)
Alright, let's go.
Let's go nail it.
Nail it.
(Tube rafting: Li Naiwen/Liu Yuning,
Wang Yuwen/Lin Yi)
Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you.
(Filmed under training and supervision)
I'm having trouble breathing, guys.
- I experienced what Naiwen said.
- No, because it's sunny here.
Indeed, it's hard to breathe.
You'll be fine once we start.
Okay.
Did you wear your glasses too low?
It's pressing on your nostrils.
Slow down.
Are we going on that one?
Yes.
Two boats?
Nai, protect Yuning.
(Me?)
Nai.
That can't be real.
Let's grab...
Grab these two.
Okay.
What posture do we take?
Just lie down.
Lie down.
(In unison)
Better not.
Slow down.
This water is like jelly.
Indeed.
Snorkeling should be quite fun.
Yes.
Superman.
Astro Boy.
Flying close to the ground.
This is also quite fun.
It feels like
really flying on the water.
Yes.
- It feels like surfing.
- Right.
We can count this
as wakeboarding, right?
- Yes.
One standing, one lying down.
(Calmed himself down)
Even holding a plank
gets tough after a bit.
My triceps are a bit sore.
It hit my mouth.
No.
♪The freezing rain
slaps my face randomly♪
So salty.
I can even get up.
(Vigorous)
Giddy-up!
What is he doing?
(Lin Yi can't lose)
A real man can do a Webster flip.
So cool.
(Yuning also tries)
Like this?
Webster flip.
Riding a horse.
- Riding a horse.
Hello.
Hold on tight.
(Guo Jingfei tries jet skiing)
Fei is so cool.
(Envious)
I'll try jet skiing.
(Feeling confident again)
I want to try jet skiing.
Let's go.
Snake-like movement.
Conquer the sea.
So salty.
Okay.
(Lin Yi, Li Naiwen)
(Deng Kai tries jet skiing)
(Li Naiwen)
I don't want to play anymore.
It's still a bit scary.
(Powered by waves)
I don't want to play anymore.
Help me.
Help me!
Help me. I don't want to play anymore.
It's too scary.
Don't move.
Okay, I won't move.
(Don't dare to move)
(Save Yuning)
(Coming to save Yuning)
I'm saved.
You can go back to the big boat
or follow them.
This boat is fine.
It's also quite fast.
Really?
Then let's go back to the big boat.
(Can't take it any longer)
That's awesome, Yuning!
Go on having fun.
(Parasailing: Sun Honglei, Yang Chaoyue)
No problem.
(Filmed safely under training
and full supervision.)
Together.
Bye-bye.
So cool.
So happy.
This is
quite impressive.
How do you feel?
Not bad.
It's fine.
Don't look down. Look forward.
Mediterranean, here we come!
Actually, when I suddenly saw you
and our teammates today,
I suddenly had a feeling. I thought
(Being sexy again)
that people really shouldn't
have internal friction.
You have to look
at the best things in your life.
Do you also think a lot
and often replay the past?
I often replay.
Me too.
Too awesome.
This is the kind of stillness
(Someone else be sexy)
you'll never find
down below.
Because
you have that feeling of looking down.
Yes.
Do you want something to eat?
I brought some.
Want some grapes?
(All about relaxation)
- Okay.
- Take some.
(Synchronized relaxation mode,
I have more)
(Nailed the enjoyment)
The Mediterranean is so beautiful here.
This part of the Mediterranean
is so beautiful.
Yeah.
Light-footed steps.
Run.
These activities are all quite fun.
Yes.
Did you play?
Took some photos. That's enough.
Thank you.
Bye-bye, thank you.
Took some photos.
You didn't ride?
I rode
about 34 seconds.
That's already very impressive.
Already 34 seconds.
(Thumbs up)
Return.
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's eat.
(Returning to the guesthouse)
(Concerned)
How was
your first water sports experience
with us?
(Happy)
So fun.
(Exhausted)
Just a bit hot.
And I was very thirsty.
(Prepared in advance)
Then you're in luck.
Try the summer limited-edition
Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon I prepared.
Pour the Chewy Lemon into the ice cup.
(Delicious drink in the making)
Perfect match for summer.
Cheers.
(Too addictive)
Ice-cold,
tangy, and so refreshing
I can't stop drinking it.
I just think
you'll definitely like it.
Like it?
(Satisfied)
I like it.
Kindred spirits.
Awesome.
It's so beautiful back there.
Blue hour.
Lin Yi is leaving.
(Lin Yi is about to return due to work)
Didn't we agree on no outfit changes?
Then why is everyone dressed to impress?
So good-looking.
You're talking about yourself, right?
We really are in our private clothes.
Yours is obviously Outfit of Today.
Mine is also private clothes.
Really?
Even your pimple patch?
A blue star.
Tonight's dinner is
self-served barbecue.
Then I should go to work.
I'll go grill it for everyone.
Ms. Wang BBQ.
Ms. Wang BBQ is amazing.
The sea breeze and waves
of the South France
always evoke all kinds of emotions.
As early as the Middle Ages,
troubadours were around here.
They used songs
to tell of life and feelings.
Next, we'll have a music challenge.
(Palm Performance)
The nine members
are divided into two teams.
Each team can send one person
as the hitter to attack.
If they fail,
offense and defense switch.
(Palm Performance: Each team sends one person for a slapping PK. If they fail, offense and defense swap. If they successfully hit the opponent's team, they perform the song according to the specified state to earn a point. The winning team serves as the hitter in the next round.)
If they successfully hit the opponent's team member,
they perform the song together
according to the specified state.
A successfully performed song
earns a point.
The winning team of each round
sends someone to be the hitter
for the next round.
No problem.
Honglei told me today
that his singing has improved.
He said it.
I was the first to sign up.
Can I team up with Yuning?
Honglei, let's do it this way.
Let Chaoyue and Wen pick people.
Let Chaoyue and Deng Kai pick.
Why?
Because they are the guest stars today.
Let's welcome the newcomers.
Right, you two can play
rock-paper-scissors to choose.
Wait, let's ask about their levels.
(Team leader's level assessment)
Chaoyue's level...
Is hard to surpass.
♪Little elephant
is a little red elephant♪
Not bad, right?
No technique, all emotion.
(A heartfelt and powerful singer)
How is Deng Kai's singing?
I'm not very good.
How's your song library?
My song library is also average.
In terms of singing,
if you had to say one thing
you're good at...
I sing with emotions.
Having emotion is enough.
That's enough.
No need for technique.
(All by emotion)
I'm telling you, this is invincible.
That works?
You two can pick your members, okay?
Pick them.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Deng Kai wins)
I choose Liu Yuning.
Okay.
(Strike first to gain the advantage)
I'll choose Yuwen.
Okay, good taste.
(Who's next?)
Just pick freely, no problem.
We've filmed together before.
Pick freely.
(Self-recommendation)
I'm especially good at slapping.
Really?
Let me try first.
Hit me.
I choose
Naiwen.
(Opportunities are earned by oneself)
Choose me.
(Same self-recommendation)
I've never lost at slapping.
Chaoyue.
This hitter is extremely fast.
Really?
Then Xingxu.
Okay.
My raising hand is useless.
Chaoyue, you didn't even consider.
Just ignored me, huh?
Yuwen's pitch was very successful.
His slaps are extremely painful.
You don't believe me? Look.
I'll show you.
(Trying again)
Come on, let's play one.
I'll hit you.
Why are you hitting me?
That gives you the first move.
Fine.
You hit me.
You can't hit me.
(Instant kill)
The scenery here is still pretty good.
You got him.
He got him.
I choose Mr. Guo Jingfei.
(Good taste)
Sure.
Your pick.
Only Honglei and Lin Yi are left.
Let's see how you choose.
(Ultimate pick one of two)
Then Honglei.
I was passed over.
(Give me an explanation)
Don't I look like someone who sings well?
Lin Yi, sing a couple lines
of Friendship Years.
Scare them.
Friendship Years.
It's Glorious Years.
Oh, Glorious Years.
♪Today, only a remnant shell remains♪
♪Welcoming the glorious years♪
Is that good?
(My head hurts)
No.
I'm just asking a question.
Because I can't really tell.
(Comfort me)
Why?
No, I'm humbly asking a question.
Is this level considered good?
(What doesn't kill me keeps hitting me)
No.
I...
Wait.
The art of language.
So sincere.
(I really didn't mean it)
Lin Yi, come on.
(Four-person team, grouping status,
five-person team)
Let's get on with it.
Let's go.
It's a guaranteed win.
Chaoyue's team is one person short.
You can be the offense first.
Who is good at slapping?
Xingxu.
Me?
(Offense: Chen Xingxu)
Okay, I'll do it.
Come on, I'll face you.
Come on.
(I will take back everything I've lost)
I'll show you the technique.
(Bring it on)
(Settle old and new grudges
in this battle)
(Offense, defense)
We'll defeat him in one go.
(Let me see)
Just one hit.
(Instantly switches to battle mode)
I'll show you the technique.
(Still an instant kill)
Okay, you got me.
Luckily it's not us.
(Performance state: pure)
Sing this song purely.
Purely.
(Hit my playlist)
♪Looking up at the sky♪
Pure.
Honglei, pure.
How about this?
Okay.
Shake it.
Twist your feet too.
Your ankle.
♪Looking up at the sky♪
♪It's a man's sky♪
♪Once under the starry sky♪
♪I was a dreaming boy♪
Star Lighting.
How was it?
(Not convinced)
What is this, you guys?
Come on, let's do a pure version.
Come on, the pure style.
Come on.
We
must have team spirit.
Come on, put your left leg
in front of your right leg.
Come on, ready, go.
♪Looking up at the sky♪
♪It's a man's sky♪
♪Once under the starry sky♪
♪I was a dreaming boy♪
♪Not knowing how high the sky is♪
♪Not knowing how far the sea is♪
How is this pure?
This is pure.
We can be even purer.
Right?
I'm super pure.
(Showing off alone)
Again.
(Pure)
♪Looking up at the sky♪
♪It's a man's sky♪
How could I not be pure?
I can be pure.
Just say if it's pure or not.
Pretty pure. Ours counts too, right?
I'm so pure that I've got goosebumps.
Everyone, look at Deng Kai's neck.
It's already red up to here.
(The honest man is going all out)
This is pure allure.
Pure allure?
What pure allure?
Pure allure has a bit more allure.
We only want pure.
Again.
Don't stick to one topic.
Give it to them.
(Current score 1:0)
Okay.
Now it's your turn.
You have to cheat to win now.
(Leave professional matters
to professionals)
(Naiwen, I'm impressed)
Wait.
You're quick.
(I'm getting serious)
I'll do it.
Defense match.
(Attacker: Chen Xingxu)
Come on.
(Defender: Li Naiwen)
I'll do it.
Come on.
(Be serious!)
(Attacker, Defender)
Did he hit you?
If you miss, they'll counter attack.
If you hit him, it's your win.
(Attack and defense swap)
It's still me.
(Defender, Attacker)
So I have to hit him.
(Just a casual thing)
(Underestimated the enemy)
What?
(Performance style: Peking Opera)
For this one, you have to use the Peking Opera style
to sing.
They don't know how.
This is my...
Come on.
(I can do it!)
(I can do it too)
We can just walk the circle.
Right.
How to sing?
How to sing this song?
How do we sing this?
♪I love to see you frown♪
♪And call me a coward♪
Ready.
(Go)
♪I love to see you frown♪
♪And call me a coward♪
(Call me a brat)
♪Your expression is more♪
♪Than a friend's flirtation♪
Is Lin Yi singing the female role?
Female role.
♪Your expression is too much♪
♪Of a lonely address♪
(Address)
That's wrong.
Lin Yi.
♪Truly one of a kind♪
♪So special♪
I'm convinced.
Convinced.
Lin Yi.
You're singing the female role.
Can we hear his bit?
A solo.
What key? I don't know the melody.
(One-on-one tutoring)
♪I love to see you frown♪
♪And call me a coward♪
Let me warm up my voice.
♪I love to see you frown♪
♪And call me a coward♪
Okay.
Really impressive.
That's the idea.
Okay.
(Current score 1:1)
Let me do it.
Honglei, you have to do it.
(Two OG members)
(Head-to-head confrontation)
Make him completely convinced.
(Defender, Attacker)
Start.
(Missed)
(In desperate need of a hole to hide in)
One more round won't hurt.
He missed, so you can counter attack.
Who?
You can go.
Go.
Pick Lin Yi.
Lin Yi's nickname is Quick Blade.
Right.
Lin Yi.
You must let her know how bad you are.
Oh, so bad?
This bad?
I'll hit you.
Oh, okay.
I'm the attacker.
(Practiced for nothing)
Okay.
His tactic is to make the opponent
laugh so hard they can't hit him.
You can't bear to hit me, right?
(What scene is this?)
Yuwen.
You can't bear to hit me, right, Yuwen.
Lin Yi, you play
so dirty.
Our teammate is ruthless.
One more move to subdue her.
Is not relying on Yuwen anymore
considered growing up?
(More moves?)
(2G offline)
What?
(2G network pecking)
He asked if he's growing up.
His whole routine.
You should do it.
It's even more gross.
Naiwen being sweet.
Right.
Why do I have to do this?
I was almost brainwashed.
Right.
I just wanted to see it.
Just now,
the moment you came over,
I wanted to hit back.
I didn't even hit you.
What do you mean hit back?
(I did nothing wrong)
Come on.
Bro, I didn't pick you.
Naiwen, I didn't pick you.
(Hahahaha)
Let her choose.
I just want to win.
Then who do you pick?
Lin Yi.
Okay.
I'll overcome it one day.
Come on, okay.
Watch out for her hitting your face,
Lin Yi.
(Really exhausted)
(Officially starts)
Quick Blade.
It's fine.
Don't be afraid.
(Quick battle, quick decision)
What's this?
(Performance mode: folk song)
Folk song style.
♪I use all♪
(Really know it?)
♪I use my whole life to support you♪
♪I hope you'll stop your wandering gaze♪
Honglei isn't singing a folk song.
Is Honglei climbing a mountain?
(Life is more than struggle)
♪Please grant me♪
♪Quiet contemplation♪
What is Yuning thinking?
I mean,
It's just a country song,
but not a folk song.
What's the characteristic
of a folk song?
You tell me.
The characteristic of a mountain song is
find someone who specializes
in mountain songs to sing it.
I can't.
(Current score 2:1)
Go.
Continue.
Yuwen.
Go for it.
(Averting gaze)
(Pretending to be busy)
This one.
I'm telling you,
my reaction is very fast.
(A master?)
(Confidence attack)
No, I'm really super fast.
You definitely can't hit me.
(This strong?)
(Want to try?)
See if he's fast.
No.
I'll switch to someone else.
Come on.
(Quick Blade returns to the scene)
No, I'm really super fast.
You definitely can't hit me.
(Cool exit)
(Really that strong?)
I won't even dodge.
(Need more practice)
What? We won, right?
No, we lost. Let them sing first.
(Instantly hit)
You lost, so why are you so graceful?
(A painful win)
Let them sing first.
Then we'll do ours.
You were being cute.
You were being cocky.
But he actually hit you.
I didn't see it at first.
I thought we won.
(Performance style: Sexy)
Sexy.
Go for it.
Let me see how sexy.
I want to see how Yuwen acts sexy.
It's a bit of a blind spot.
You can't stretch the philtrum.
Why can't I stretch the philtrum?
I am Li Naiwen.
Is that sexy?
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Stretch your leg.
(Sexy guidance)
(I'll close my eyes for now)
♪The rights and wrongs of love are too many♪
♪Arriving at an exuberant occasion♪
♪Hurry, speak.
Once spoken, it's most bare♪
Yuwen, sing it like you mean it.
Rehabilitation exercise.
(I'm uncomfortable)
♪Whether you love me or not, ignore me or not♪
♪It affects the outcome♪
(We did it!)
Go barbecue.
We won.
You go barbecue.
No.
Wang Yuwen failed.
If you can, you do it.
No, Wang Yuwen failed.
You do it.
He's like, "Although I can't,
she can't either."
Wang Yuwen can't.
You guys do it.
Let's think of
a way that's sexier than theirs, okay?
Come on.
Let's be neat.
(DENG KAI)
(LIU YU NING)
(GUO JING FEI)
(LI NAI WEN)
(Can't hold it in)
So greasy.
Lin Yi is good at this.
Lin Yi is good at it.
(LIN YI)
(Keep it low-key)
Give it to them.
(We don't want it. Current score 2:2)
These four over here
are indeed very sexy.
Fei is a little fly.
(Rubbing hands like a fly)
Or a raccoon.
Rubbing hands.
Come on.
Continue.
Who do I hit?
Up to you.
Then I'll definitely...
Come on,
Chaoyue.
It's okay, Chaoyue. Don't be afraid.
I'll hit you.
Come on.
Come on, hit.
Who does that?
Don't grab me.
I'm not.
She's digging her nails into me
The nails are digging in.
Like a cat.
Here we go.
(Hit)
It's fine.
No problem.
Bragging.
(Act out the state: Bragging)
Okay.
Fei can do this.
How to act bragging?
How about we do one line each?
Okay.
You go first.
Wait. I'll go first?
Just thumbs up to the sky.
♪These years haven't been good or bad♪
♪Just that someone has been missing♪
Dude, I'm not bragging.
In this whole area,
I'm telling you.
♪And I'm gradually understanding♪
♪You are still my unchanging concern♪
Come to me if you need anything.
(Brothers in heart)
♪How much love♪
♪Can be relived?♪
Really?
♪How many people♪
♪Are worth♪
♪Waiting for?♪
♪When love has weathered all the years♪
♪Is there still courage♪
♪To love?♪
Not bad.
Good.
(Current score 2:3)
Not bad.
Lin Yi.
Lin Yi has also hit, right?
Lin Yi hasn't hit.
I was hit.
You haven't hit?
Try this one again.
To become bad,
first overcome your fear.
Just pick the one you fear the most,
the fiercest one.
What?
Right.
It's fine.
Just imagine
that he teaches you every day,
and everything he says is wrong.
Now hit him.
Isn't that a good thing?
Isn't it a good thing
he teaches me every day?
The key is that everything
he says is wrong, you know.
Okay.
Through-the-Back Fist.
Through-the-Back Fist. Come on.
Are you trying to hit me to death?
Swing it.
So strong.
This can't be
the last episode I'm recording, right?
It's fine, Lin Yi.
You'll definitely pack up
and leave tomorrow.
Honglei.
It's just about the game, Honglei.
Just about the game.
Well,
I tend to overthink.
It's okay.
Don't pressure him.
No.
No pressure at all.
Then I'll be bad.
(This palm strike will be crazy)
Let's see how bad you are.
You two are a combo.
(Lei and Bad)
You are Bad, and he is Lei.
Start.
(Solidly)
Did you see Honglei's reaction?
He couldn't believe it, you know?
So scary.
Awesome.
Call your ex.
This is so hard.
(Act out the state: Call your ex)
Call your ex.
Ready? Go.
♪I can't forget you♪
♪I write you in my diary♪
♪Give me a pink memory♪
This won't do.
I acted so seriously.
You were playing with snap pops.
They were all tragic.
Playing with snap pops?
I was flinging snot.
I even heard the snap.
Why is it like Chinese New Year?
Right, it was my tragic scene.
Who flings like this?
Like this?
I'm blowing my nose.
Don't play with snap pops again.
Slam dunk.
Dunked on my knee.
Yuwen.
That's provocation.
(The brain is going crazy)
Here we go again.
She's thinking of words.
I see through her.
We just dunked on his knee.
I want to counterattack.
Yuwen.
I'm still thinking.
I can't think of anything.
She's about to let her
hometown dialect sing.
(Rhyme count: 1)
But we'll still be the ones who win.
(Rhyme count: 2)
Guess that's just the way we swing.
(Rhyme count: 3)
You're just a pack of little things.
You got it?
Awesome.
(Very handsome five little things)
That's the vibe.
That's enough.
We let you win.
Okay.
You won't lose sleep over it.
That's enough.
That's a fierce payback.
Okay.
(Current score 2:4)
I'll do it.
Come on, me and Xingxu.
Let's do it.
(Defender and attacker)
Start.
Do you want to win?
(Hit)
So fast?
Isn't it a bit too fast?
Doesn't it hurt?
Do you want to win?
(Full damage to the stomach)
No.
I pulled back super fast.
I actually pulled back very fast.
You hurt yourself.
(Act out the state: sincere)
How about this? Let's do it together.
We're singing this song for Lin Yi.
Come on.
Let's sing sincerely.
Come on, let's do it together.
Come on.
♪I want to say goodbye to you♪
♪Because maybe I'll never see you again♪
♪Tomorrow I will leave♪
♪The familiar place and you♪
♪We're about to part,
and my tears are falling♪
♪I will firmly remember your face♪
♪I will cherish
the memories you gave me♪
♪The days in my heart♪
♪Will never be erased♪
♪I can't promise you♪
♪That I will come back♪
♪Without looking back♪
♪I keep going without looking back♪
Love you all.
Because Lin Yi is leaving everyone
and going back to China first.
We really can't bear to see him go.
Tonight,
let's have Lin Yi and his teammates
prepare a sumptuous
barbecue dinner for everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you, Lin Yi.
He grills it himself,
and we don't help, right?
Dare you eat it?
Come on.
Let's go. Let's eat.
Lin Yi is leaving tomorrow.
How can you do that?
Huh?
(Surprise delicacy drops)
Lin Yi,
look, there's a pineapple here.
Aren't these Dicos'
Volcano Pineapple Burgers?
(Craving)
How is it?
Super juicy.
My Golden Rice Burger
is very delicious too.
The freshly fried rice cake
is super good.
And it's the kind that gets better
the more you chew.
There are whole chicken legs too.
Let's share them with everyone.
We'll continue to eat these
when we return home.
It's still warm.
These skewers are huge.
I'll do it.
Alright, it's still us two.
It has to be us two.
(Ms. Wang BBQ is open)
Two beef and two chicken.
Let's get them going.
They cook faster.
Open for business.
(Wow The World BBQ shop
officially opens)
I'll help you.
Okay.
These look really good.
What kind of meat is this?
Chicken, I guess.
Chicken.
It looks so delicious.
Right.
What is this?
Mushroom sauce.
Creamy mushroom sauce.
What's inside?
Mushrooms.
What's in the mushroom sauce?
These button mushrooms are so big.
(Super big mushrooms)
So big.
Is this a button mushroom?
Right.
When did it get so big?
I don't know.
It...
Zhangjiakou mushroom.
Has it mutated?
Then it can fill a bowl directly.
Fill a bowl of soup.
Right. Eating one, I'd probably be full.
How can this mushroom be so big?
I've never seen it either.
It's like a hat.
Just grill it like this.
After grilling,
it'll release juice inside.
It'll definitely release juice.
It'll release juice.
Lin Yi, what time is your ride?
What time are you leaving from here?
Four o'clock.
(What's up, bro?)
We'll stay with you.
(Really?)
We love you so much.
I'm crying.
I'll really cry in a bit.
Cry away.
Let it cook a little longer.
Then we can cut it.
Cut and then grill.
I mean the pork belly.
It needs a long time to grill.
These are all big chunks.
Brush on this.
(Brushing on the soul sauce)
This piece is almost done.
This piece.
It's done.
It's definitely cooked.
Let them take it away.
Just one piece?
Lin Yi,
you take the first piece.
Thank you.
(Happy)
Is it good?
Yes, it's yummy.
The chicken is good, right?
All done.
It's good, right?
Very tender.
(Amazing)
This chicken is so good.
This chicken is really good.
Not just ordinarily good.
Right?
(Full of praise)
The chicken is extremely good.
You two can have a taste.
The quality of the chicken is very good.
The chicken...
How can the chicken be so tender?
Okay, take this plate first. Here.
You eat that mushroom.
Take this plate away.
I'll do it.
Let's eat while we grill.
Let's not wait
till it's all cooked to eat.
(Food's coming out)
(Comfortable)
(Rewarding the BBQ chef)
Thank you.
Two pork
and one chicken.
Really good.
This vegetable wrap.
Okay.
Come on, go.
Give this to them.
You are so good to me.
(Full plate of eggplant left ungrilled)
Not a single eggplant has been grilled.
(Of course)
Today is
No Eggplant Day.
Will you come for the last episode?
I'll come.
I only have a few days off.
A perfect combination
of color, aroma, and taste.
These must have some secret seasonings.
Definitely.
At a beautiful home
in Marseille
by the Mediterranean,
we are using the Northeast barbecue's
secret sauce.
Right?
Not really.
It's also local.
Local sauce.
But the Northeast grilling method.
(Northeast BBQ chef here)
Dandong barbecue.
Get some Northeast barbecue.
What is Northeast barbecue?
Northeast barbecue.
You can put...
Barbecue grilled by Northeasterners.
Right, so it's called
Northeast barbecue.
What I grill is Jiangsu barbecue.
(Connects the dots fast)
Let's go.
Let's eat.
This is fish soup.
(Bouillabaisse)
Their local specialty.
Come on. If you want to drink,
I'll serve it for you.
Want to drink?
I want to try it.
Here.
Thank you.
Come on.
Welcome, new friend.
Farewell,
(Old Friend Lin Yi)
old friend.
Farewell.
(Dusk holds Marseille's sea breeze,
joyfully waiting for the next meet)
Come back quickly, Lin Yi.
See you soon.
(Next Episode Preview)
Let's test your tacit cooperation.
What are you laughing at?
You're looking for a companion.
The problem now is where to put it.
Am I leading you guys?
Honglei, it's too fast.
If you believe
in my observation ability,
then it's
Honglei.
It's also possible that both of you are.
I think it's you two.
They might be on the same side.
I
am just a commoner.
A bunch of Wow The World veterans
got played by little Balloon Spirits.
(Who are the Balloon Spirits?)
Don't forget to buy
dinner ingredients, everyone.
This looks good.
It's really tasty.
You ate it all?
Let's just press peanuts for oil.
Press with what?
(Teasing Nai)
With peanuts.
Just press them.
(Can't believe it)
Peanuts?
(Hahahaha)
Let's buy a jug of oil.
Is that okay?
Absolutely.
Is it tasty?
It's good.
Let's cook eggplant.
We're missing Lin Yi.
(Please stay tuned
for Earth Group's cooking)
Follow the Light.
For the first member to complete it,
we have prepared a mysterious gift.
What matters most
is that we stick together.
He's the most ruthless.
He's fiercer than anyone
when he gets going.
(Lights out)
It's so dark.
This is mine, bro.
(Lights out)
Who is it?
Who?
What are you doing?
Why are you taking mine?
Who gave this to me?
Who threw this into my hand?
(Lights out)
Who?
Don't step on me.
The button is so hard to fasten.
(Who will win in the end?)